I think I'll go for a walk outside, ma'am The summer sun knows be my name
I hear him now, I just can't stay inside all day I gotta get out, give me some of those rays
Everybody's smiling, sunshine day It's actually not very sunny, it's very foggy
I think I'll go for a walk every day now.
Da-dum-da-dum-da-dum.
What's another Brady song?
I gotta keep on, keep on, keep on moving.
Keep on, keep on, keep on grooving.
Hi, lady.
I'm like Tommy James.
I'm waving at everyone and being unmoxious.
You learned that from me.
You learned that from watching me.
It is a sunshine day. It's a sunshine. I think I got
Every day now. It's a beautiful day. I'm gonna say hi to everybody
I'm not gonna ask them if they're selling poop fish, but I mean, I'll be a little friendlier
Not gonna get kicked out of a bed a bed store with one poor lady working there are no customers at all
I mean it's like
Okay
I mean, honestly, Tommy James, you know why I don't want you on my show?
Because you suck!
It's so mine.
I made a beautiful video with you in a night in shining armor.
I made a big, the night, the armor has a big belly on it.
There's all these ginger hairs and got Alexandra.
Like that, right?
Yeah, it's not funny.
The funniest things I've ever seen in my life.
Oh, don't get me started on that dolphin again.
Okay, I need to get, I need to order my fries real quick.
You got a bunch of snow?
Oh, look, look at this.
The life, we're at the library.
Hold on, I'll be right back.
I need to get my fries, hold on.
Darn it. They're out of the hot honey and biscuits. Hello. Okay
I was gonna get a hot honey and biscuit
Now I like the hot honey. I like it when it burns my tongue. Oh
It's about to hit by a car
I'm gonna need a couple cheeseburgers
Ba da ba ba ba I'm loving it
Look there's a look at it's my lucky day. Look at the lucky truck. I
Got some lucky energy today. You see that look at the lucky truck. I
Don't want to get in trouble. This is my hometown McDonald's. I got banned from here. I'll start with that really. Oh
Okay
What do you guys want order anything you went off the menu
Okay, what do you guys want from McDonald's?
Do they want crocs?
This is not that great. I just got double cheeseburgers. No cheese?
You run in traffic. I can run in traffic. Hey, I know how to run.
the McBanger? Is that a racist joke? Because, you know, Banger, it says N-G-E-R in the word
Banger. You know that? I notice things like that now.
What's the toy? What's Crocs?
What a croc, you know Christine told her own son go jump off a bridge, and then she said
He did but it's been to like an alligator invested pond or something. It's a very confusing story. I don't quite know
Thank you corruption
It was a very confusing story first of all, why would she say that to her son second of all
If she said it, why would she then say don't?
Well, that's for me.
Thank you so much.
You're very welcome.
Have a great day.
You too.
Bye-bye.
I mean, but she did say jump off a bridge.
It's okay.
Christine, I said sacrifice babies in the woods.
You can tell me to jump off a bridge, okay?
Oh, I eat my cats.
I never have never will
It was a weird story though
Anyway, it's a good coffee and I go to liquor store cars
But you know, they're saying oh, I was so drunk is a scum. Hey, first of all
Really?
I don't really drink.
Beta.
You don't really drink?
Almost every time I hear you, you are so fucking drunk as a skunk.
I can't even barely hear your high-pitched Minnie Mouse voice.
whatever they call, whatever those juice boxes.
I mean, it's like, I had one and a half of them
throughout the entire evening,
because I was up midnight to like, you know,
six in the morning.
It's like six hours and like two drinks.
How many wings have you built on the White Claw factory?
How many wings have they built?
How many cars do the executives of White Claw own?
just based on on your on your monthly consumption and
You're telling me I only he's drunk. I
Mean that was a little bit ridiculous and what was it anybody saying anything to her? Oh
We'll be that you're a you're not only a drunk. You're a mean drunk. I mean, maybe I'm a sober
But yeah